pokerstars-online.com 2015-09-06

# Poker Stars - Online Poker Software Privacy Policy - Privacy Issues

* As part of the Site account opening process and to allow us to provide services to you, we will ask you to provide us with certain personal information, including your name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address and password as well as to certify that you are at least 18 years old or older in jurisdictions in which the minimum age for use of the Service is greater than 18. For the purposes of using the Service via the Mobile Software, you will be required to consent to the use of location-based services (LBS) by us to detect your geographic location. We may also use your information to verify your credentials from third parties including financial institutions, identification verification agencies and credit reference agencies for the purposes of us providing services to you. In addition, when you use the Service we store certain personal information, including information on your activity on the Site and information held on Devices (defined below) or systems that you use, to allow us to enhance the services that we provide to you. We, members of our Group, our affiliates and third parties providing services on our behalf will use your personal information for various purposes such as: 

  * to confirm financial transactions,
  * to provide services to you;
  * identification and vetting purposes;
  * statistical analysis and research;
  * research and development;
  * marketing, market research and customer profiling;
  * data analysis;
  * to comply with licensing and regulatory requirements; and
  * to analyse your credit and fraud risk.

We may disclose your personal information: 
  1. if required to do so by law or by regulatory authority;
  2. if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary: 
    1. to comply with any law or comply with legal process served on us; 
    2. to protect and defend our rights or property;
    3. to any regulatory body or licensing body or authority;
    4. to third parties for the purposes of settling or making payment in connection with any wager;
    5. to any payment management or debt collection company engaged by us to handle payment and collection processes to and from Users; 
    6. to third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf; 
    7. to any third party that purchases us or our business or any part of us or our business;
    8. to credit reference agencies as described in the circumstances described below in this Section 2;
  3. with your consent;
  4. for the purposes of disaster recovery; or
  5. as set out in Sections **5** and **6** below.

We and other members of our corporate Group may occasionally send you events and news information or information regarding new services and to provide you with customer support services. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter.

Where you fail to reimburse us for any chargebacks, denial or reversal of deposits you make, we may give details of your accounts and how you manage them to Credit Reference Agencies (CRA).  The CRA will record the outstanding debt. This information may be supplied to other organisations and  records will remain on the CRA file for 6 years after the date of the chargeback, denial or reversal of payment. The information will be used by the CRA to prevent crime, fraud, money laundering, verifying your identity if you, your partner, other members of your household, your business or financial associates apply for other facilities, monitoring the operation of accounts you may hold, making decisions for credit, credit related or other facilities, trace your whereabouts, recover debts that you owe, statistical analysis and system testing.

Your personal information may be processed by us, other members or our Group, our affiliates, our agents and third parties providing services to us, in jurisdictions outside of the Isle of Man and the European Economic Area.  In this event we will comply with the terms of the Isle of Man’s Data Protection Act 2002.

We will only use your name in publicity materials with your consent.

The name you register with us must be your own name. In addition, it is very important that you complete the account details with valid information, since it will be used in the course of validating financial transactions and the other aforementioned purposes. You are required to advise us of any relevant changes to your personal information.

Users are able to change account details by selecting an account option in the downloaded software.
